http://www.glass-ts.com/privacy-policy

Privacy policy
We respect your privacy and will treat your personal data no
differently to the confidential work that we conduct on behalf of our
clients.
This policy explains how we treat the data that we
collect from individuals who visit our website, subscribe to our
newsletter, contract our services or engage with us in other ways.
In
addition, we have also included links to publicly available guidance
and information relating to privacy, cookies and browser settings to
help you in making informed decisions when browsing our website and the
wider internet.
About us
Glass Technology Services Ltd is a
company registered (No. 02832216) in England and limited by guarantee.
Glass Technology Services Ltd is the data controller of any data
submitted to us or collected from you. Our registered office is at the
address below:
Glass Technology Services Ltd          9 Churchill WayChapeltownSheffieldSouth YorkshireS35 2PYUnited KingdomTel:
+44 (0) 114 290 1801Fax:
+44 (0) 114 290 1851Email:
enquiries@glass-ts.com
Social Media: Twitter (@GlassTesting)
Visitors to our website
When you visit www.glass-ts.com we use Google Analytics to collect industry-standard internet log and usage information of the site, including visitor behaviour patterns. The purpose of this is to enable us to monitor traffic, the popularity of different types of content, help us to optimise the site and improve our service to clients and visitors.
The information collected is processed in a way which does not identify anyone. We do not make, and we do not permit any other organisations to make, any attempt to determine the identity of anyone who visits our website.
Google’s servers are based in the United States and are covered by the Privacy Shield framework. For further information, please see the Google Analytics privacy policy.
We occasionally require support from our web developers (Prototype Creative Ltd) to maintain or improve the website. Website usage information (Google Analytics) may be made accessible for the sole purpose of resolving issues and assisting in optimisation of the website.
Please also see our cookies policy.
Making an enquiry with us
If you submit an enquiry to us you will submit data by doing so – whether this is through our online enquiry form, by direct email or telephone. This data is used only for the specific purpose of responding to your enquiry - we will not add you to any communication and marketing lists, unless you expressly opt-in or request this.
We may log your enquiry on our internal systems for the purpose of tracking that the enquiry has been responded to, to follow-up with a quotation or provide the support requested by you. We will monitor enquiry trends, but this is anonymised and is limited to data that is not personally identifiable.
No data is processed by or shared with any other organisations and we will never share your details. Personally identifiable data will be deleted from our systems after a period of twelve months of inactivity, except where an enquiry leads to an order with us where it will be used for the purpose of delivering on the contract.
Placing orders with us
To conduct work on your behalf we will require certain corporate and, where necessary, personal data in order to communicate with you, for billing purposes and for addressing certain technical reports and other documentation. This data is collected from you for the sole purpose of delivering the agreed contract work.
We may contact you in relation to the agreed work and for feedback on our performance. By placing work with us you will not be added to any mailing lists for the purpose of marketing.
Receiving communications from us
We would like to keep in touch with our clients, as well as other interested parties, and we do this by providing an newsletter and occasional emails about service updates and other news.
You may consent to receive such information by joining our mailing list. As part of the registration process for this we do collect limited personal information. During registration, and at any time after, users can unsubscribe fully or change their preferences as to which information they would like to receive.
We collect this information for a number of reasons: to send you the requested information (e.g. newsletter or service updates), to check that our records are correct and to contact you if you require additional information. We will never rent or sell this information to any other organisation or business.
We use MailChimp to collect and manage this data and to deliver the requested information. MailChimp also allows us to review performance data – such as email open rates and clicks on featured links or content. This performance data allows us to monitor and improve the content that we provide.
MailChimp’s servers are based in the United States and are covered by the Privacy Shield framework. For further information, please see the MailChimp privacy notice.
We occasionally require support from our web developers (Prototype Creative Ltd) to manage integration of subscriptions with our enquiry and newsletter sign-up forms on the website. Access to our MailChimp account may be made accessible for the sole purpose of ensuring functional integration of such forms in the website.
You can unsubscribe from these mailings at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any such email or by contacting us.
Participation in surveys
You may be invited to participate in surveys – for example to collect feedback on your experiences of working with us or to carry out market research. In these situations we may utilise a service such as SurveyMonkey to host the survey and process the associated data. We will not share, sell or rent any personal data submitted in such a situation, nor do we permit SurveyMonkey or other third parties to do so.
SurveyMonkey’s servers are based in the United States and are covered by the Privacy Shield framework. For further information, please see the SurveyMonkey privacy policy.
Access to your personal information
You are entitled to access any personal information that we hold on you. To make a request please contact us by post or by emailing us.
Links to other websites and use of social media
This privacy notice does not the cover any use of other websites, including social media. We may link to external websites in order to provide you with related information, but please be aware that any external websites are not governed by this privacy notice and, if you have any questions about how they collect or use your information, you will need to check the privacy notice for that website. Privacy notices should be easily accessible to visitors and are typically found on the footer of any webpage.
Changes to this privacy notice
We regularly review our data protection policy and website privacy policy. This current notice was issued on 24/05/2018.
How did you hear about us?
Choose an optionGoogle or other web searchWord of mouthPress news/editorialAdvertisingSocial mediaOther (please specify)
Other
Message
I have read and agree to the privacy and cookie policies
Send
